<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>knotes.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">KNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">KNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">KNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Knotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKNotesxx</name>
  <description>
    <p>
      KNotes is a program that lets you write the computer equivalent of sticky notes.
      The notes are saved automatically when you exit the program, and they display when you open the program.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KNotes és un programa que permet escriure l'equivalent informàtic a les notes adhesives. Les notes es desen automàticament en sortir del programa, i es mostren en obrir el programa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KNotes is a program that lets you write the computer equivalent of sticky notes. The notes are saved automatically when you exit the program, and they display when you open the program.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KNotes es un programa que le permite escribir en el equipo el equivalente de notas pegajosas. Las notas se guardan automáticamente cuando usted sale del programa y se muestran cuando lo abre.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A KNotes program használatával kisebb jegyzeteket lehet készíteni. A jegyzetek a programból való kilépéskor automatikusan mentésre kerülnek, a program indulásakor pedig ismét megjelennek.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KNotes는 메모를 남길 수 있는 프로그램입니다. 프로그램을 종료할 때 메모를 자동으로 저장하고, 다음 실행 때 보여 줍니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Mit KNotes kannst Du so wat as Anback-Notizen för den Reekner maken. De Notizen warrt bi't Utmaken vun't Programm automaatsch sekert un wedder wiest, wenn Du dat Programm wedder opröppst.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Knotes is de digitale variant van de gele zelfklevende notitieblaadjes. De notities worden bij het afsluiten automatisch bewaard en worden weer getoond wanneer het programma gestart wordt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KNotes jest programem, który umożliwia tworzenie w komputerze tzw. żółtych karteczek. Takie karteczki są samoczynnie zapisywane przy wyjściu z programu i pokazywane przy otwieraniu programu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KNotes é um programa que lhe permite escrever o equivalente para computadores das notas autocolantes. As notas são gravadas automaticamente quando sair do programa e as mesmas voltam a aparecer quando o abrir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">KNotes é um programa que lhe permite escrever no computador da mesma forma que usa notas autoadesivas. As notas são gravadas automaticamente quando você sai do programa e depois apresentadas quando você abre o programa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KNotes je program, ktorý vám umožní písať na počítači ekvivalent "sticky notes". Poznámky sa ukladajú automaticky keď ukončíte program a potom sa zobrazia pri otvorení programu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KNotes je program, ki vam omogoča pisanje lepljivih sporočilc na računalniku. Sporočilca so samodejno shranjena ob izhodu iz programa in prikazana ob odprtju programa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Knotes är ett program som låter dig skriva datorns motsvarighet till klisterlappar. Anteckningarna sparas automatiskt när programmet avslutas, och visas när programmet startas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KNotes — це програма, що дозволяє створювати комп'ютерний еквівалент липких листочків із нотатками. Нотатки автоматично зберігаються під час завершення роботи програми і показуються при її запуску.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKNotes is a program that lets you write the computer equivalent of sticky notes. The notes are saved automatically when you exit the program, and they display when you open the program.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Szolgáltatások:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">기능:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Markmalen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Caracteristici:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Write notes in your choice of font and background color</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Escriu les notes amb el tipus de lletra i el color de fons de la vostra elecció</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Write notes in your choice of font and background colour</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Escriba notas en el tipo de letra y color de fondo de su elección</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Jegyzetek írása tetszőleges betűtípussal és háttérszínnel</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">사용자 정의 글꼴 및 배경색 지원</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">De Notizen mit Dien Schriftoort un Achtergrundklöör schrieven</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Schrijf notities met uw keuze voor lettertype en achtergrondkleur</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Pisanie notatek według własnego wyboru czcionki i koloru</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Escrever notas à sua escolha, com determinados tipos de letra e cores de fundo</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Escrever notas com a fonte e cor de fundo de sua escolha</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Písanie poznámok podľa vášho výberu písma a farby pozadia</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Pisanje sporočilc s pisavo in barvo ozadja po meri</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Skriv anteckningar med eget val av teckensnitt och bakgrundsfärg</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">запис нотаток бажаним для вас кольором і шрифтом на тлі бажаного кольору;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxWrite notes in your choice of font and background colorxx</li>
      <li>Use drag and drop to email your notes</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Usa arrossega i deixa per enviar les vostres notes</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Use drag and drop to email your notes</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Use arrastrar y soltar para enviar sus notas por correo</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Jegyzetek elküldése e-mailben a fogd-és-vidd módszerrel</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">드래그 앤 드롭으로 바로 이메일 보내기</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Notizen över Trecken un Afleggen mit Nettpost loosstüern</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Slepen en neerzetten gebruiken om uw notities te e-mailen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Używanie przeciągania i upuszczania do wysyłania pocztą swoich notatek</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Arrastar as notas para as enviar por e-mail</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Arrastar e soltar as notas para envio por e-mail</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Použitie drag and drop na poslanie vašich poznámok</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Pošiljanje sporočilc preko e-pošte s pomočjo povleci/spusti</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Använd drag och släpp för att skicka anteckningar med e-post</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">використання перетягування зі скиданням для надсилання ваших нотаток електронною поштою;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxUse drag and drop to email your notesxx</li>
      <li>Can be dragged into Calendar to book a time-slot</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Es poden arrossegar al calendari per a reservar un horari</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Can be dragged into Calendar to book a time-slot</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Puede soltarse en el calendario para reservar un tiempo</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Naptárba húzható egy időablak lefoglalásához</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">달력에 드래그 앤 드롭으로 일정 추가</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Laat sik na den Kalenner trecken, wat en Stoot Tiet reserveren deit</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Kan versleept worden in Agenda om een time-slot te boeken</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Możliwość przeciągnięcia na kalendarz celem zaplanowania przedziału czasowego</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Pode ser arrastado para o Calendário para agendar um espaço de tempo</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Pode ser arrastado para o calendário para agendar um espaço de tempo</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Je možné potiahnutie do kalendára na rezervovanie termínu</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Sporočilca lahko povlečete v koledar in rezervirate določen termin</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Kan dras till en kalender för att boka en tidslucka</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість перетягування нотаток до календаря для створення запису планування;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCan be dragged into Calendar to book a time-slotxx</li>
      <li>Notes can be printed</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Les notes es poden imprimir</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Notes can be printed</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Las notas pueden imprimirse</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">A jegyzetek nyomtathatók</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">인쇄 기능</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Notizen laat sik drucken</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Notities kunnen worden afgedrukt</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Możliwość drukowania notatek</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">As notas podem ser impressas</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">As notas podem ser impressas</li>
      <li xml:lang="ro">Notele pot fi tipărite</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Poznámky je možné tlačiť</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Sporočilca lahko natisnete</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Anteckningar kan skrivas ut</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість друку нотаток.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxNotes can be printedxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=knotes</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdepim/knotes/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/knotes.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>knotes</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
